<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string-array name="trivia">
    <item><![CDATA[For the movie the Wizard of Oz, Judy Garland was paid $35 a week while Toto received $125 a week.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[The producers of the movie Gone With The Wind were fined 5,000 dollars for allowing the word “damn“ to be heard within the movie‘s dialog.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Brooke Shields spent a lot of time during the filming of Blue Lagoon standing/walking in a trench beside Chris Atkins so that she wouldn\'t be taller than him in the scenes that they had together.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[The Blues Brothers once held the record for crashing the most police cars in a movie at approximately 30. The record was eventually broken by Blues Brothers 2000.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[During filming of the chariot race scene in the movie Ben-Hur, one of the cameras was completely ruined when a chariot ran over it. The footage right up to the camera\'s obliteration was used in the final film.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Near the beginning of the movie Back To The Future there’s a scene where they show all of the clocks at Doc\'s house. If you look closely there is one clock with a little man hanging from the minute hand.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[In Carrie, the slow motion scene at the end of the movie was filmed in reverse to simulate ghostlike movement effects. If watched vigilantly, cars can be seen driving backwards in the upper left hand corner of the screen.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Bogart never said "Play it again Sam" in the movie Casablanca. What Bogart did say was "Play it Sam".]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Orson Welles was only 21 years old when here starred in & directed in the movie Citizen Kane.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[When the Mother-Ship passes over the Devil\'s Tower near the end of Spielberg\'s movie, Close Encounters of the Third Kind, R2-D2 can be seen hanging from the bottom of the ship.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[In the movie E.T. there is a scene where the young boy lures the extraterrestrial with some Reese\'s pieces. Originally Spielberg was going to use M+M\'s, but he could not get the rights. Reese\'s pieces were the replacement.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[The Godfather was the first movie in over twenty years in which Marlon Brando was required to audition.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA["Halloween" was originally going to be titled "The Babysitter Murders".]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[The Sesame Street characters Bert and Ernie were named after the cop and the taxi driver from the movie “It\'s a Wonderful Life”.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[The mechanical shark used in the movie Jaws was nicknamed Bruce, named after Spielberg\'s lawyer.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[When the T-Rex devours the traffic light in San Diego within the movie “The Lost Word: Jurassic Park“, there is a sign close by that reads "No Dinosaurs".]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[After reading the script for Men in Black, Will Smith did not want any part of the movie. It was wife Jada that persuaded him to take the part.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Midnight Cowboy was the first non-pornographic movie to receive a X rating.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Marlon Brandon received $4 Million for his 10-minute role in the movie Superman. No one (that is still alive) knows who supplied the voice of God in the epic The Ten Commandments.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Due to the amount of violent acts shown "Red Dawn" was the first movie to be handed the PG-13 rating.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[All 3 lead actors from the film Rebel Without a Cause died under tragic circumstances. Natalie wood drowned, James Dean died in a car crash and Sal Mineo was stabbed to death by a stranger.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Kevin Spacey and Mike Myers were both considered for the role of Inspector Clouseau for 2006 movie Pink Panther.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Most of the distant shots of the submarines seen in the movie “The Abyss” are models.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[The carpet designs seen in Sid\'s hallway in Toy Story are the same as the carpet designs seen in "The Shining."]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[The story of Mulan had been told in China for almost 1,500 years before Disney picked it up and made it into a movie.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[The ruby red slippers seen in the movie "The Wizard of Oz" once sold at an auction for $660,000.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Hitchcock used chocolate syrup to portray the blood seen in the shower scene for his classic film Psycho.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Over 1,400 actresses were interviewed to play the part of Scarlett O\'Hara for the movie Gone with the Wind.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[The first toilet being flushed in a motion picture was in Alfred Hitchcock’s movie Psycho.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[In the James Bond movie “For Your Eyes Only” one of the bond girls used to be a man.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[The longest Hollywood kiss was from the 1941 film, "You\'re in the Army Now". It lasted for three minutes and three seconds.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Disney\'s "Beauty and the Beast" was the first animated film to be nominated for an Oscar for best picture.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Liverpool is the most filmed British city.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Bruce Lee was so fast, that they actually had to slow a film down so you could see his moves.]]></item>
    <item><![CDATA[Rolling Stone Keith Richards was set to make a cameo appearance as the father of Captain Jack Sparrow, in Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man\'s Chest, a commitment he could not keep.]]></item>
  </string-array>

</resources>
